Contact

autumn_bentley@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/autumnbentley-bsn-msn-nmel-941343108 (LinkedIn) crossroadshospice.com (Company)

Top Skills

Hospitals
Nursing
Clinical Research

Languages

English

Honors-Awards
Top Nurse

Autumn Bentley BSN MSN-NMEL

Travel RN Case Manager at Nuclear Care Partners Cincinnati. Ohio Area

Summary

Experienced Case Manager with a demonstrated history of working in the health wellness and fitness industry. Skilled in Healthcare Information Technology (HIT), Hospice & Palliative Medicine, Nursing, Inpatient Care, and Clinical Research. Strong community and social services professional with a MSN Executive Leadership and Management focused in MSN Executive Leadership and Management from Sacred Heart University.

Experience

Nuclear Care Partners
2 years 7 months
RN Case Manager
January 2018 - Present (2 years 7 months)
Ohio

Registered Nurse February 2018 - Present (2 years 6 months) Ohio

Core Medical Group
Case Manager
September 2017 - Present (2 years 11 months)
Pasadena, Maryland

Crossroads Hospice
Assistant Clinical Director
August 2015 - August 2017 (2 years 1 month)

Summit Behavioral Health RN February 2015 - August 2015 (7 months) Cincinnati Children's Hospital Medical Center Child and Adolescent Psychiatric Staff October 2012 - October 2014 (2 years 1 month)

Select Specialty Hospitals PCA 2010 - 2011 (1 year)

Education

Sacred Heart University

MSN Executive Leadership and Management, MSN Executive Leadership and Management · (2015 - 2016)

The Christ College of Nursing and Health Sciences BSN, Nursing · (2011 - 2014)

Colerain High School (2002 - 2004)